247solitaire.com 2019-06-12

# 247 Solitaire Privacy Policy

We collect basic information such as, but not limited to, IP address, hardware configuration, and browser type.

When connecting to facebook, we access basic profile information, which includes name, profile picture, gender, networks, user ID, list of friends, and any other information you've made public.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website
  * To send periodic emails
  * The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer a better site experience in the future.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

<https://www.247games.com/support>
